be more than a little suspicious of
Russia. But then the European countries
from my way of looking at it has
more reason to support Ukraine than anything
Israel has located in the Middle East.
their enemies. So they always always have
held Israel back from winning.
It is true. Then Yes, it is. And when
as far as European countries are concerned, you can
certainly not saying they always have
logic and logic say logic says that
it is actually a logical fallacy that
appeal to the majority opinion in a
question.
>> Yes, but don't you agree that it
existence. If you look at the old one
Shain in Iran who was very loyal
practically puppeteered and ate the US like that
he realized at the end of his reign i
an interview with CBS News he said that